Jayottam Jadhav

Principle Engineer

Details

Mumbai, India

+91 84510 53264 jayottamjadhav@gmail.com

Date of Birth 26/June/1987

Skills



Languages



Other

GitHub: jayottam

Website: jayottam.com



Professional summary

Principle engineer having 8+ years of experience in building scalable web application using plethora of technologies. Over last 9 years I have demonstrated exceptional skills in project/product building while leading the team from the front and coaching them to be the next leaders.

Employment History

Principle Engineer at Loginext Solutions Pvt Ltd July 2017 - August 2019 | May 2020 - Present

Understanding the business needs in detail and build technical solutions accordingly, keeping product nuances in mind.

Owning the technical solutions end to end and follows up on the engineering debts.

Handling production releases with Devops and production troubleshoots on architecture and infra level.

Application Lead at Insta Remedy & Technology Solutions Pvt Ltd October 2015 - July 2017

I had build this product from scratch, have experience of building the entire web and mobile app and it's databases using different technologies such as Java, Spring JDBC, Hibernate, MySQL, AngularJS, Rest APIs.

Team Lead at Planfirma Technologies Pvt Ltd October 2012 - October 2015

Planfirma is a service based company, in which I had opportunity to build applications for dozens of clients in various domains from scratch, domains such as FinTech, ERP, Asset Management, Ecommerce. This was my founding stone, which had given me exposure beyond measure and positioning me for the success.



Education

PGDM - IT Project Management (DLP) | *Distinction* Welingkar Institute of Management, Mumbai 2015 - 2017

Bachelor of Engineering (B.E.) Mumbai University 2008 - 2011



Certifications

Scrum Master - PSM 1 Verification Link - https://www.scrum.org/certificates/381098 Jun 2019